Friday night bailout packs
Matching skirts and bubble attacks
Shots lined up like a firing squad
Steering like it's a gift from God
Selfie sticks and broken heels
Twerking to songs they don't even feel
Hair extensions, mobile fry
Echoes like a battle cry
Blue girls, break the sound
Every bar becomes battleground
Raise a glass and raise your pitch every
Another glitch
In the matrix of your brain
Guessables of drunk disdain
Blue girls, breathe for fame
But no one here remembers your name
One just cried, no one knows why
Another's making out with some finance guy
They laugh at memes from 2012
And call it slay, just kill me now
Shots for brunch and brunch for clout
More nags now scream and shout
But they stash his glitter bobs
When the list is mixed with bottle bonds
Blue girls, break the sound
Every bar becomes battleground
Raise a glass and raise your pitch every
Another glitch
In the logic of the night
Every cheer just kills the vibe
Blue girls, dance and scream like chaos
In a forever 21 dream
Who will have soup up in my sheets?
Ooh, the last night just tapped me in the open
I'm bashing at me, come on, cheers, sweet boy
Blue girls, queen to cringe
Makes my eardrums sing
Fart out from attention short
I'll ride in a jukebox court
Blue girls, couple send
'Til the hangover makes amends
Blue girls, you rule the scene
With a scream that haunts my punk rock dreams
I'll ride in a jukebox court
Blue girls, come on, cheers, sweet boy